http://www.stihlusa.com/products/blowers-and-shredder-vacs/professional-blowers/br600/


With its powerful, fuel-efficient engine, the BR 600 MAGNUM® sets the standard for professional-grade blowers.
It produces the highest air volume and velocity of all our backpack blowers, yet features a low-emission engine,
making it a great choice in both urban and rural areas. No matter where the job takes you, the BR 600 MAGNUM® 
blower is the ideal choice for heavy-duty cleanup.