http://www.littlebeaver.com/products/hydraulic-earth-drills/

Hydraulic Earth Drills

    Powerful, reliable, reversible hydraulic drive
    Torque-free digging eliminates kickback
    Highly maneuverable three-wheel chassis

Applications:

    Industrial fencing
    Landscaping
    Pole barns
    Soil sampling
    Groundwater monitoring
    Mobile home & light utility anchoring
    Foundation pier holes
    Horizontal boring


By combining higher horsepower engines with the reversibility, reliability and convenience of hydraulic drive, Little Beaver Hydraulic earth drills are ideal
 for drilling in rocky or heavy clay soils. With their extra torque, these powerful earth drills can handle augers up to 16″ in diameter and can drill depths 
of up to 30´ with 12″ or smaller diameter augers, depending on soil conditions. A forward/reverse lever lets you remove the auger if it gets caught under an obstruction,
 such as a rock or tree root.

Even with all this power, most hole drilling remains a one-man operation, thanks to our exclusive torque tube.
The torque tube eliminates the kickback common with competitive earth augers, making one-man drilling safe, fast and productive. 
Convenient front and rear handles make it easy to load the Hydraulic earth auger into and out of your truck.