http://www.woodchippers.info/bandit_90.shtml

This rugged, compact 9 inch diameter capacity chipper meets the needs of most jobs for tree services, contractor's and homeowners.

The model 90 is built tough with a powerful dual feed system.  This unit features a wide 17 inch chipper opening and has the power to pull whole trees into the chipper.  
So, if you are looking for a high production, yet compact hand fed chipper than the 90 is for you. 







The Model 90XP has a distinguished career of well over 20 years, serving tree care professionals, rental companies and municipalities needing a productive,
 cost-effective, and durable chipper. Whether working brush clearing, utility clearing, or rental duties, this fleet-favorite features a large 9-inch wide by 17-inch 
tall opening and a standard dual-wheel feed system in Bandit’s proven Slide Box Feed System. It’s extremely productive and efficient in processing large amounts 
of brush at once, as well as big limbs and small trees.